[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community
So for that first review, they had product sentiment predicted as 1,
对于第一条点评 对于这个产片的情感预测是1
let's take a look at that review.
让我们来看一下这条点评
So I'm gonna look at the giraffe_reviews.
我要看giraffe_review
The first one is 0, the index 0, and let's look at the actual text of the review.
第一条是0 索引为0 让我们看一下这条点评的具体的文本内容
Okay, I'm gonna read this to you a little bit.
我会读一下内容
It says, Sophie, oh Sophie, your time has come.
这个点评说了 Sophie带来的美好时光
My granddaughter, Violet is 5 months old and starting to teeth.
我的孙女Violet 5个月了 已经能开始长牙了
What a joy for little Sophie.
把Sophie 带给Violet
Little Sophie brings to Violet.
是多么一件快乐的事啊
Oh Violet really loves Sophie [SOUND].
Violet 真的很喜欢Sophie
Sophie is made of very pliable rubber that is sturdy but not tough.
Sophie是用很软的橡胶做的 很坚固但是并不硬
And it's quite easy for Violet to twist all her positions and put it in her mouth.
这样Violet就能够轻易的扭动位置 然后把它放到嘴里
Okay, that's the right positive review looks like.
这应该是一条正评价应该有的用样子
She write a poem about Sophie.
她写了一首诗给Sophie
Let's look at the second placed review here.
让我们看看第二条评论
So tihs is the, for element 1, so it's the second element on the table.
应该是位置1的对象（但其实第二个表中的对象）
And let's look at what that review looks like.
让我们看看这个评论有什么
And here's what it says, I'm not sure why Sophie is such a hit with the little ones,
它说了我不确定为什么Sophie对于小孩子这么有吸引力
but my 7 month old baby girl is one of the adoring fans.
但是我7个月的小女儿真的是超级喜欢Sophie
The rubber is softer and pleasant to handle.
香蕉真的很软 摸起来很舒服
My daughter enjoy chewing on it, [SOUND] on the legs, chewing on the legs,
我的女儿咀嚼它的时候真的很享受 咬它的腿
nubs of the head.
它的头
So these ears get chewed and so on.
然后它的耳朵 等等
[SOUND] She really loves it and she loves that squeaky, so
它真的很喜欢复读的功能
apparently it's a big hit.
显然Sophie很吸引我的女儿
So this is two positive reviews.
所以这是两条正面评价
Now let me show you a little python trick which you can use to show
让我给你演示一下 Python的小技巧 这样你就能看到
the most negative reviews.
负面评价了
So the most negative reviews are at the bottom of the table.
最负面的评价在表格最底部
So we could ask what is the length from the table and
我们可以先找到表格的长度
find the last element and so on.
然后找对最后一个对象
But with python, we can do this really easily.
对于Python来说 我们可以很简单的就做到
So let me show you what's happening next.
让我给你演示一下
Show most negative reviews.
显示出最负面的评价
So we can take this table and just index it with a negative number, minus 1.
我们把这张表加上索引 用上负数 -1
And what that does is it goes to the end of the table.
这样就是表格的最后的对象了
So minus one is the last element,
-1是最后一个对象
minus two is the second to last element, and so on.
-2是倒数第二个对象以此类推
So let's look at the most negative review for our giraffe.
让我们看看长颈鹿玩具的最负面的评价
And I forgot to put a quote here, so let's just do that and execute.
我忘了用引用符号了 让我们先执行
Okay.
好
Here's a negative review about poor Sophie.
这是Sophie最负面的评价
My son loved Sophie.
我的儿子喜欢Sophie
I bought one for every baby shower I've gone to.
我给每一个孩子都买了一个
Now, my daughter is 6 months old just today nearly choked on it.
但是我6个月的女儿几乎把它吞了
Now I'll never give it to her again.
现在我不会再给她Sophie了
So the problem is this person's daughter is really scary,
这个人的女儿的问题真的很吓人
almost choked by trying to swallow this giraffe.
因为她女儿几乎因为把这个长颈鹿玩具给吞了下去而窒息
And so you see a negative review of somebody talking about how this giraffe,
你可以看到这边有不少负面评价说道
which is a lovely chewing toy, is also a choking hazard.
这个长颈鹿作为一个咀嚼玩具 有被吞食的风险
Let's look at the second most negative review.
让我们看看倒数第二条评价
So again, giraffe and minus 2,
恩继续 用-2 这个索引
second most negative review and we'll take a quick look at it.
第二条最负面的评价 我们来看一下
So one thing that people don't like about it is it might be a choking hazard.
它说了 人们不喜欢这个东西的原因就是因为有被误吞的风险
So let's see what this one says.
让我们仔细看看这人怎么说的
This children's toy is nostalgic and very cute.
这个玩具还是很可爱的
That sounds pretty positive.
发出的声音也很好
Even the second most negative review starts pretty positive.
就算是第二个负面的评价 也是以正面评价开头的
However, the distinct rubber smell and very old odd taste.
但是 这个橡胶闻起来 尝起来有点奇怪
Yes, I tried it.
我试过了
So this person tried to chew his or her kid's toy.
这个人试着咀嚼了他儿子的玩具
That my baby did not enjoy.
我的孩子并不喜欢
So apparently, the rubber smells and
很显然是因为 橡胶闻起来的味道
this person wasn't able to clean it.
还有就是这个人没办法去清理异味
And the kid did not like it.
然后小孩不喜欢
And they overpaid for this toy.
他们觉得这个玩具并不值得这个价格
So the second thing that people complain about is that this is a smelly toy.
所以说第二个负评价 抱怨了 这个玩具有异味
Smells okay to me, but could be an issue.
也许对我来说可以接受 但是还是有问题
Okay, so now in a few lines of code, we build a sentiment analysis.
所以说通过几行代码 我们建立了一个情感分析模型
A system that can actually look at reviews and really sort them and
一个可以去观察点评 并且把他们排序的系统
show really positive and negative aspects of this particular product.
能够显然一个产品的正面和负面的模型
[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community